[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Arnaldo] I'm jealous of your close
friendship with this
Lily Cruz.
I'm not talking about
the Lily Cruz that you're with.
[Arnaldo] She's an impostor.
That's right.
[Arnaldo] I'm going to make her regret
all the things that she did to me.
And then, I'll kill her.
[Anna] What happened to Lily?
-I have to go save her!
-There's a bomb, everyone!
-[woman] There's a bomb!
-[Julio laughs]
It was just planted here to scare you.
[grunting]
[Diego] Lily's life is in danger.
I'm coming with you, Diego.
[Diego] I promise I'll bring
back Ivy safe and sound.
[Jepoy] Diego, I'll come with you.
[Arnaldo] You're Lily Cruz,
right? Answer me!
Yes! I am Lily Cruz!
[Damian] You need to stay there so we know
Julio Ardiente's every move.
That's the only way
we can take everything from him.
[Diego] Arnaldo! Put the gun down!
No! If I can't have her, you can't either.
-Arnaldo!
-No!
-[gunshot]
-[Ivy screams]
[Ivy] Get out of here.
I'll take care of this.
-I'll bring him to the hospital.
-[Jose] Congressman.
-Something happened to the mayor.
-What?
He's in critical condition
at the hospital.
[tense music playing]
[Damian] I'm back, Raul.
Your reign as Jaguar is over.
[police siren wailing]
[Damian] Mr. Cop!
Catch me if you can!
-Mr. Cop!
-[gunshot]
[tense music playing]
[gunshots]
[honks]
[screeching]
[police officer] Get out!
Put down your gun!
[Damian] Take it easy!
Dante! Dante!
I need your help.
Get me out of here.
I've told you so many times
but you still haven't changed.
When will you learn your lesson?
When you're dead?
What are you so proud of?
It's not like you're getting
anything out of being a lawyer!
Money isn't the reason
why I chose to be a lawyer.
I became one so I can put
all criminals like you in jail.
Brother or not, I'll have you locked up
if that's what it takes
to set you straight.
Then you're a useless brother,
you bastard!
My family and I are leaving.
We'll start over somewhere far away.
You're abandoning me.
Damian, I'm begging you.
Please change. I can't help you anymore.
Then leave. You talk like you're all that!
I don't need you, Attorney Cruz.
I can get out of here on my own!
And you can forget
that you have a brother!
Get out!
-[indistinct shouts]
-[grunting]
[grunting]
[guards blow whistle]
[Rufo] What's going on?! Stop that!
That's enough!
[police officer 2] Stop! Stop!
-Aren't you going to stop?!
-[Damian grunts]
Follow me! Stand up!
[police officer 2] Stubborn, eh?
-Take care of that!
-[police officer 2] Yes, sir.
I'll take care of him.
[reporter] A prisoner escaped
prison after a riot
broke out at the City Jail.
Give me the keys or I'll put
a hole in your head.
Hand it over.
[reporter] In other news,
a sports car was stolen
by unknown men in Quezon City last night.
[Damian] Rufo, hurry up.
-[siren wailing in distance]
-I can see the police cars.
[Damian] Let's go!
Drive faster, donut hogs!
-[gunshots]
-[Damian laughs]
[reporter] An SUV was stolen
by thieves in Makati last night.
[reporter] According to reports,
the leader of the group
responsible for many crimes
in Metro Manila calls himself the Jaguar.
[Damian] Looking good!
[Rufo] Mr. Jaguar.
What's with our new get-up?
This look suits us because
we're in the big leagues now.
[laughs]
Stealing cars got old real fast.
I want us to enter…
smuggling, kidnapping,
gambling, extortion,
and illegal drugs!
Are we going to go against big syndicates?
We'll take them all down.
[laughs hysterically]
[Damian sighs]
[car screeches]
[Damian] Get down!
[man] What's this?!
What's the meaning of this?!
[man] We didn't do anything wrong!
[Rufo] Follow him!
-[screeches]
-[Rufo] Hurry!
-[henchman] Okay.
-[Damian] Buboy!
[ominous music playing]
[Rufo] Put your guns down!
Sir, have mercy, sir.
-Rufo--
-[henchman] Have mercy, sir.
[Damian] I feel sorry for him.
[gunshot]
[laughs hysterically]
I thought I emptied it.
[gun clinks on ground]
[henchmen] Move! Get out! Hurry up!
[Damian] Take everything!
[laughs hysterically]
[gunshots]
[Rufo] Mr. Jaguar!
The police tracked us down.
We need to leave this place.
[guns firing]
[Rufo] Let's go!
[police siren wailing in distance]
[gunshots]
[Rufo] Hurry and get the car!
Mr. Jaguar, let's get out of here!
[Damian] Go! Leave!
-But, sir!
-Take care of this. Hurry!
Let's go!
[Damian] Leave now!
[policeman 1] Stop!
[policeman 2] Put your hands up!
Go and handcuff him!
Sir, Ouch!
Ouch!
[policeman 1] Where's Jaguar?
He went there. He ran away, sir.
-[policeman 1] Get him.
-Carry me! Carry me! Ouch!
[Rufo] Boss. All our money's gone.
The police took everything.
Our operations have to continue
so we can recover our losses.
[Damian] Find someone
who'll pretend to be
Jaguar while I'm here.
Boss. Can't I do it?
Rufo, you're still young.
You can't do it yet.
We need someone who has experience.
Someone who has connections
with powerful people.
Someone who knows
how to run a syndicate too.
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone ringing]
[Damian] Raul Torillo?
Yes. Who's this?
It's Jaguar.
Have my people talked to you yet?
Yes. Why?
Now you know why I called.
Hold on. Let me ask you.
Why did you choose me?
Because I want to take
your family's gambling den.
[Damian] Word on the street is,
that you don't like them.
So, if you want to get even with them,
I will support you.
You provide the money.
I'll provide the people and the guns.
All you have to do is pretend
to be Jaguar while I'm in prison.
It'll benefit us both. It's a win-win.
[Damian] Now get ready, Raul.
The original is back.
And nothing beats the original.
[Emilia] Arnaldo! Arnaldo! Doc!
[Claire] Ivy!
[Ivy] Arnaldo!
-[Claire] What happened?
-[Ivy] Mamita.
Doc, where's Arnaldo?
How is our son? Please, please!
The operation was successful.
[doctor] We were able to extract
the bullet out of his head.
Right now, he is in
a medically-induced coma.
And that is to give time
to his brain to heal itself.
[Claire] Coma?
[doctor] Mayor Arnaldo is very lucky
he did not incur
any vital brain tissue damage.
Colonel.
Ms. Aguas, come with me.
[tense music playing]
Why? Congressman?
-[Jose] Come with me.
-No! Stop it!
Hey! That hurts!
-Ouch!
-Stand here!
[Ivy] Ouch!
Congressman! What's the meaning of this?!
Tell me the truth, Ivy.
Who shot Arnaldo?!
It was a man!
A man shot Arnaldo!
I was going to help him,
but it was too late!
He shot Arnaldo and got away!
You didn't recognize him?!
How could I when he had
a bonnet on his face?!
[tense music continues]
-[grunts]
-You and Arnaldo
were the only ones on that yacht.
It was you! You were the one
who shot my grandson!
You! You were the one
who tried to kill Arnaldo!
[tense music swells]
[Julio groans]
[grunting]
[Ivy] I didn't--
Go ahead.
[tense music swells]
Do it, Emilia.
If I inject this into you,
you'll be the first one to die.
Your heart will be the first one to go.
Do you want that?
I'm not the one who shot Arnaldo!
Put that down. Put that down!
I'll say it again.
I'm not the one who shot Arnaldo!
If you don't believe me,
then go ahead! Kill me!
I admire your bravery,
Ms. Aguas. Do you play poker?!
Because how I'd love
to call your bluff right now!
Colonel! Take her out of here!
Take that woman away!
Just try and fight back! Out!
That damned liar!
[Camia] Diego, why did you leave Lily?!
You put her life in danger!
Don't you know what
the Ardientes could do to her?!
Auntie, we had no choice.
Lily would've been discovered--
When Arnaldo wakes up, Lily's done for!
The Ardientes will kill her!
What time is she supposed to call?
[Diego] Before the night ends.
If she doesn't call,
I'm going with you to the Ardientes.
-[Diego] Auntie. Auntie.
-[Anna] Auntie.
-[heart rate monitor beeping]
-[oxygen machine running]
[somber music playing]
[beeping continues]
What have they done to you?
You aren't going to die, Arnaldo.
Not on my watch. You are not going to die.
I won't be burying my own grandson.
I'll be the one to say
when you should die.
You don't die until I say so!
Whoever did this will pay, Arnaldo.
You fight… You fight for your life!
You're not supposed to die.
[door opens]
[somber music continues playing]
[tense music playing]
[henchman] Stop resisting!
I said, stop resisting!
[grunting]
[buzzing]
[tense music swells]
[henchman] Get her inside. Hurry!
Let's go.
Lock the door.
We're now at Ardiente Hospital
where Mayor Torillo
is currently confined
after being shot in the head
by an unknown assailant.
Congressman…
Can you please tell us what happened?
Someone tried to murder
my grandson.
[Julio on TV] We don't know who.
Someone tried to
assassinate him.
[reporter on TV] So, how is he doing now?
He's in a coma right now.
But I know my grandson.
He's a fighter.
He won't give up that easily.
The only thing I ask of
our people right now
is to please pray for
his speedy recovery
from his current status.
Is it true that the mayor was
with Ms. Ivy Aguas
during the incident?
Yes.
[reporter on TV] Where is she now?
May we ask her for a statement?
Ivy Aguas was the sole witness
to that incident.
And that's why we've decided
to hide her, for her safety.
Her life is already in danger.
Whoever tried to murder my grandson…
will most likely target Ivy next.
Liar. Where is my daughter?!
Tell us where she is!
[Jose] Congressman,
the CCTV cameras were
turned off at that time.
[Jose] It's possible that
Miss Aguas shot the mayor
but it's also possible that she didn't.
The police are conducting
an investigation, Julio.
I don't care about them.
We'll conduct our own investigation.
[Julio] Colonel, I don't know
how you're going to do it,
but I want you to get
a copy of the ballistics report
of the bullet
that shot Arnaldo in the head.
And I want you to look
for other witnesses.
Right away, sir.
Papa, what do we do with Ivy Aguas?
I will interrogate her
until the truth is forced
out of that woman's tongue.
I promise you, this night
won't end without me finding out
who is going to pay for
what happened to my grandson.
[man] There's a 500,000 peso
reward for anybody
who can provide information
about what happened
during the mayor's shooting.
Who here knows about what happened?
You.
Do you know anything?
[tense music playing]
Ivy, call us before the night is over.
-If you don't
-All right, I will.
we'll attack the Ardientes ourselves.
What time is it, Diego?
When are we leaving?
[Jepoy] I can't stay here!
What are we doing?
-Let's go.
-Diego, are you going to find Lily?
-Yes, auntie.
-I'm coming with you.
-No, Auntie.
Anna, stay here.
We won't take long. Let's go.
[Camia] Guard, ready the car. Quickly.
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music playing]
[tense music swells]
[tense music continues]
[grunting]
[tense music playing]
Diego, Jepoy.
[breathing heavily]
Those damn Ardientes.
Are you ready?
Let's do this.
[cell phone buzzing]
[whispering] Wait, wait.
[Diego] Hello, who is this?
Diego?
Hello, Ivy? Where are you?
Ivy?!
Um…
Here. I'm with
the Ardientes.
Don't worry, I'm safe.
We're at the hospital.
We'll save you from them.
Don't.
Diego, don't.
Umm…
I'm safe. I couldn't call right
away because I forgot my phone.
About Arnaldo…
Don't worry. He's in a coma.
He can't rat me out.
Diego, please, don't do anything
that might get you killed.
Do you understand me?
Don't do anything
-that can get you--
-[phone beeps]
Ivy? Ivy?!
[sighs]
Diego, they're leaving.
Come on.
[whispering] Jepoy, wait!
What are you doing, Diego?! Jepoy!
[Jepoy] What?! Diego?
What's going on?
Diego.
[Jepoy] Diego!
Jepoy, Ivy called. She's safe. Let's go.
-Let's go!
-Are you sure?
Yes!
-[Anna] Auntie?
-[Camia] Anna.
[slow tense music playing]
Arnaldo is like a ticking time bomb.
Lily will be in grave danger
once he wakes up.
[Camia] We must speed up our plans.
[Anna] But Miss Cora is our
only witness against Emilia.
[Anna] And we don't know where she is.
But we know her address.
I'll sneak into her house
in Sitio Nueve and look
for evidence against Emilia.
Sitio Nueve?
[Jepoy] Diego, the residents
there are pro-Ardiente.
If they see you, they'll mob you.
Why not ask someone else to do it?
No. I won't involve others in this.
I'll keep you guys posted.
I'll help you.
[Diego] No, Anna.
It's too dangerous.
[phone chimes]
Boss?
Tell all the guards to be on alert.
Someone else is posing as the Jaguar.
Yes, boss. Understood.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Raul] I'm so close
to bringing Julio down.
So I won't give you back your title.
It's mine now.
I am the real Jaguar.
And you're the impostor.
[suspenseful music swells]
[Mahjong tiles shuffling]
[Raul's henchman 1] Good evening, boss.
Boss, what brings you here?
Our operations are running smoothly.
-Is there a problem--
-[gunshot]
[screaming]
[Raul's henchman 3]
Boss?! Why did you do that?!
[Raul's henchman 2 grunting]
[Damian's henchman 1] Hands up!
[Raul's henchman 3]
You aren't the real Jaguar!
You're the impostor!
[Raul's henchman 2 groaning]
[Damian] Freaking morons!
The man you call "boss"
is the impostor. I am the real Jaguar!
And starting today,
this gambling den is mine,
and you'll work for me!
Now, to those who refuse, raise your hand.
Raise your--
You refuse?
-Don't!
-[gunshot]
[laughs hysterically]
He's dead!
Where's Rufo? Why isn't he here?
Boss Jaguar took care of him.
Because he betrayed us.
What?
Your fake boss is the real traitor here.
[Damian] Tell him to give me back my men,
my money, my weapons, women,
and all the properties
he acquired under the guise of Jaguar.
Because if not,
I will paint Poblacion Ardiente
red with his blood!
Is that clear, morons?
I can't hear you!
[gunshot]
-We'll tell him.
-Very good!
[laughing hysterically]
Jepoy, I think you should lie low for now.
[Diego] Yes, Ivy can cover
for you from the Ardientes,
but sooner or later,
they'll find out that it was you
who shot Arnaldo.
I don't care about the Ardientes, Diego!
I won't run away from them.
If I have to kill for Ivy, I'll do it.
Jepoy, they'll stop at nothing
to take you out. You know them.
Yes, I do.
[tense music playing]
[groans]
[tense music continues]
[phone clatters]
Sit down!
I can sit myself down!
[Jose] Tie her up.
Oh, hello, Ardientes! You're back.
Did you miss me already?
Yada, yada, yada, yada, yada…
Leave us.
This is between me…
and her.
Go. Don't worry.
I can take care of myself.
You have two options, Miss Aguas.
Either you tell me the truth…
[whirring]
or watch me unleash hell.
It's your choice.
Do you remember what we did to Madrigal?
You'll experience
something worse than that…
if you do not tell me about
everything you did to Arnaldo.
You really are getting old, Congressman.
I told you, didn't I?
I did not shoot Arnaldo!
[whirring]
They say the eyes tell the truth
and the mouth lies.
I can see it in your eyes…
all the horrible things
you did to my grandson!
[drill whirring]
[tense music playing]
Go ahead! Kill me!
Kill me.
But if you do, Arnaldo
will go completely insane.
If you kill Ivy Aguas,
Mister Mayor will never get well.
If you kill me, it'll be like
you killed your own grandson.
Your only real grandson!
[whirring]
Go on! Do it!
-I want the truth!
-You want the truth?!
Why don't you have me take a paraffin test
to get this over with?!
Maybe that'll finally convince
you that I didn't shoot Arnaldo!
You hear me?
I hear you, silly girl.
I'll give you one chance.
I'll wait for you here, Congressman.
But hurry. I can be really impatient.
Silly girl.
You're not going anywhere!
You're all tied up!
For now. But I might surprise you.
Go help old grandpa walk.
[Julio chuckles] Nice try, little girl.
I love you too!
[tense music continues]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[tense music continues]
[Ivy breathes heavily]
[man] Congressman,
we'll take these
to the crime lab for analysis.
When will we get the results?
[man] Tomorrow, Congressman.
[Emilia] What? I can't wait
till tomorrow, Papa.
Wait, let me handle it.
I'm going to do something
for us to know
the truth this very evening.
[tense music plays]
What do you have in mind?
Let me handle it, Papa.
[tense music swells]
Listen up, Ivy Aguas…
I'm sure you've known all
this time how much I hate you.
But the thing is, you're so good
at bluffing and telling lies.
You've actually mastered them.
So, I'll have you undergo
a lie detector test
to reveal the truth.
You can never be too careful.
Dishonesty is contagious.
And I'm really scared
that I'll catch your disease.
It's fatal.
Well, I guess what they say is true.
Paranoia is contagious.
But I understand, Emilia.
And I feel bad for you.
Because after all the crimes
you've committed,
you think everyone else is out to get you.
Excuse me? You know, believe it or not,
you're the only one on this
whole planet I'm suspicious of.
[Emilia] Just you.
Too bad you're just insecure
because you see me as a threat.
[chuckles]
[Emilia] Is that how highly
you think of yourself?
Me? Insecure of you? Wrong.
Excuse me, I still wear the crown.
Then keep it.
-But I have the throne.
-Fine.
Let's see where that arrogance
takes you after we reveal
all the dirty secrets
you've been keeping from us.
I'm not keeping any secrets.
Well then, good.
[snaps fingers] Shall we start?
[suspenseful music playing]
Okay. First question.
Is your name Ivy Aguas?
Yes.
Okay. Second question.
Do you have plans
to bring down the Ardientes?
What kind of question is that?
Of course, not--
-Just answer it!
-I don't!
Third question.
Are you Diego Torillo
and Camia Cruz's spy?
Never.
Hmm…
Okay. Next question will be…
Are you the one
who planned Arnaldo's downfall?
I would never do that to him.
Were you the one who shot Arnaldo?
No!
But you know who shot my son! Yes or no?!
Answer my question!
[Julio] One wrong answer…
and you're dead.
Do I have to keep repeating myself?
I already told you
that I didn't see the face
of the man who shot Arnaldo!
Come on. Tell me she's lying.
Her heart rate and blood
pressure are normal.
She's telling the truth.
[laughs]
[Ivy] See?
Okay?
So, Emilia?
Do you have any more questions?
Go ahead and ask them.
Otherwise, you're just wasting our time.
One last question.
Are you ready?
[tense music plays]
Are you Lily Cruz?
[tense music swells]
Are you Lily Cruz?!
Emilia, what does that have to do with--
Just answer the damn question!
Are you Lily Cruz?!
I am not Lily Cruz!
Tell me. Tell me she's lying!
-She's telling the truth.
-Oh, come on!
Check the machine! Maybe it's defective!
Have them check your head too!
That's what's defective!
Not their machine.
Even if the results of that
damn machine don't change,
you can never change what I think of you!
You can lie straight to my face,
but you can never ever fool me!
Are you done?
Emilia, since you've asked
all of your questions…
Now, it's my turn.
You see, liars supposedly
hate other liars too.
Why don't you sit here
and take the lie detector test?
Because maybe you're
the one keeping secrets…
from your family.
Let's find out the truth!
So we'll know who the real liar
is between us.
Okay, what's the result?
Come on! Give it to me now!
I want to hear it!
Again?
He already gave you the results!
You're stupid and deaf.
What?! It's still the same?!
[tense music playing]
[shouts]
[Ivy] You think you can
outsmart me, Emilia?
Sorry to say, but I'm smarter than you.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make my plans succeed.
Don't ever try to challenge me, Emilia,
because I'll never let you catch me alive.
[suspenseful music playing]
Well?
Aren't you going to do or say something?!
Why? What do you want me to do?
Oh, come on. I can't believe this, Raul!
You don't want to make Ivy pay
for what she did to Arnaldo?!
Why would I do that?
She proved her innocence, didn't she?
And you believed that?!
I don't believe things
that easily, Emilia.
I need to know the truth first
before I make a move.
-That is so weak!
-Watch what you say.
You're crossing the line!
Well, Raul, if you won't do
anything about it, then, I will!
I'll talk to someone
and that's the Jaguar!
Don't do that, Emilia.
You don't know that bastard.
Emilia!
[ominous music playing]
Your paraffin test came back.
It was negative.
I'm not surprised.
[Julio scoffs]
Don't celebrate just yet, Miss Aguas.
You may have passed all the tests…
but that doesn't mean you're off the hook.
It may be true that
you didn't shoot Arnaldo.
And it might be true
you didn't see the face
of the person who did that to Arnaldo.
But that doesn't mean…
you didn't want to have him killed.
You better be careful, Ivy.
Don't let me catch you
because my bullet
is faster than your karma.
If I wanted to kill Arnaldo,
I would've done that a long time ago.
So, next time, Congressman,
think twice before making
false accusations against me,
because you don't know
what I'm capable of!
[suspenseful music playing]
Watch your words, Miss Aguas!
Because this knife's sharper
than your tongue.
[tense music swells]
[somber piano music playing]
[Ivy] It doesn't matter if
I suffer or get tortured.
I can take the pain if it means
I can protect my loved ones.
Please spare them.
[dramatic music playing]
[Jose] Congressman.
Yes?
Someone wants to talk to you.
Who is it?
Tell the Congressman everything you know.
I'm Chito, the caretaker
of one of the yachts
docked near the site
where the mayor was shot.
I came to you first.
I haven't gone to the police yet.
What do you know about what happened?
[gunshot]
[Chito] I heard several gunshots
that night.
[Diego] Come on, Jepoy. The lights are on.
[Diego] I hope they're here.
Hurry, come on!
[tense music playing]
[gunshots]
[Chito] After that, I saw two
men fleeing the crime scene.
I'll never forget their faces.
Congressman, we asked an artist
to make a cartographic sketch
based on the witness' description.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Jose] It's Diego Torillo
and your former employee, Madrigal.
[suspenseful music swells]
[Julio] One million for Madrigal's body.
And another million for Diego's corpse.
[Cora] My conscience keeps eating at me.
I'm ready to divulge
Mrs. Emilia's corrupt activities.
[Julio] I will go against Diego Torillo.
I will run for governor.
[Ivy] This election's going to be
dirtier and bloodier.
Jepoy and Diego's lives are in danger.
Julio has issued a shoot-to-kill order
-against them.
-[gunshots]
-[women screaming]
-Get down!
-[gunshots]
[people screaming]
[Camia] What's happening?!
Mom!
[theme music playing]